<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chanity</string>

    // splash screen
    <string name="splash_iv">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="chanity_iv">Chanity Logo</string>

    // welcome
    <string name="WelcomeTitle">Welcome to Chanity!</string>
    <string name="RegisLogin">Please register or login first.</string>
    <string name="getstarted">Get Started</string>
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string name="title_welcome_page">Welcome to Chanity!</string>

    // register login
    <string name="copyright">© 2022 Chanity</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="name">Username</string>
    <string name="title_signup_page">Ready to create your account?</string>
    <string name="title_login_page">Welcome back!</string>
    <string name="message_login_page">Welcome back :)</string>


    // home
    <string name="home1">Check your personality by taking this test!</string>
    <string name="home2">The Big Five personality test measures the five personality factors that psychologists have determined are core to our personality makeup. The Five Factors of personality consists of:</string>
    <string name="start_test">Start Test</string>
    <string name="ocean_iv">Ocean Image</string>

    // test
    <string name="test1">Answer each question according to how well it describes you. </string>
    <string name="get_result">Get Result</string>
    <string name="question1">I am the life of the party.</string>
    <string name="question2">I feel little concern for others.</string>
    <string name="question3">I am always prepared.</string>
    <string name="question4">I get stressed out easily.</string>
    <string name="question5">I have a rich vocabulary.</string>
    <string name="question6">I dont talk a lot.</string>
    <string name="question7">I am interested in people.</string>
    <string name="question8">I leave my belongings around.</string>
    <string name="question9">I am relaxed most of the time.</string>
    <string name="question10">I have a difficulty understanding abstract ideas.</string>
    <string name="question11">I feel comfortable around people.</string>
    <string name="question12">I insult people.</string>
    <string name="question13">I pay attention to details.</string>
    <string name="question14">I worry about things.</string>
    <string name="question15">I have a vivid imagination.</string>
    <string name="question16">I keep in the background.</string>
    <string name="question17">I sympathize with others feeling.</string>
    <string name="question18">I make a mess of things.</string>
    <string name="question19">I seldom feel blue.</string>
    <string name="question20">I am not interested in abstract ideas.</string>
    <string name="question21">I start conversations.</string>
    <string name="question22">I am not interested in other peoples problems.</string>
    <string name="question23">I get chores done right away.</string>
    <string name="question24">I am easily disturbed.</string>
    <string name="question25">I have excellent ideas.</string>

    <string name="question26">I have little to say.</string>
    <string name="question27">I have a soft heart.</string>
    <string name="question28">I often forget to put things back in their proper place.</string>
    <string name="question29">I get upset easily.</string>
    <string name="question30">I do not have a good imagination.</string>

    <string name="question31">I talk to a lot of different people at parties.</string>
    <string name="question32">I am not really interested in others.</string>
    <string name="question33">I like order.</string>
    <string name="question34">I change my mood a lot.</string>
    <string name="question35">I am quick to understand things.</string>

    <string name="question36">I dont like to draw attention to myself</string>
    <string name="question37">I take time out for others.</string>
    <string name="question38">I shirk my duties.</string>
    <string name="question39">I have frequent mood swings.</string>
    <string name="question40">I use difficult words.</string>

    <string name="question41">I dont mind being the center of attention.</string>
    <string name="question42">I feel others emotions.</string>
    <string name="question43">I follow a schedule.</string>
    <string name="question44">I get irritated easily.</string>
    <string name="question45">I spend time reflecting on things.</string>

    <string name="question46">I am quiet around strangers.</string>
    <string name="question47">I make people feel at ease.</string>
    <string name="question48">I am exacting in my work.</string>
    <string name="question49">I often feel blue.</string>
    <string name="question50">I am full of ideas.</string>


    // option menu
    <string name="language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="radio1">Very Inaccurate</string>
    <string name="radio2">Inaccurate</string>
    <string name="radio3">Neutral</string>
    <string name="radio4">Accurate</string>
    <string name="radio5">Very Accurate</string>
    <string name="result_greeting">%s your primary trait is %s</string>
    <string name="percentage_tv"><u>Percentage Result</u></string>
    <string name="result_ocean">OCEAN Result</string>
    <string name="percentage">%s{%}\n\n%s{%}\n\n%s{%}\n\n%s{%}\n\n%s{%}</string>

    <string name="desc">%s</string>
    <string name="strengths">Strengths</string>
    <string name="strengths_tv">%s</string>
    <string name="weaknesses">Weaknesses</string>
    <string name="weaknesses_tv">%s</string>

    <string name="o_desc">The sub-traits of openness personality trait are: Imaginative, adventurous, have high emotionality, have high artistic interests, intelligent and liberalism.</string>
    <string name="o_strength">Easy to collaborate with.\nCreative.\nLove to learn something new.\nOpen to diversity.\nGive great attention to mental imagery.</string>
    <string name="o_weakness">Easily swayed.\nTheir ideas are often unconventional.\nMany of them are often unpredictable.\nTend to avoid positions that need to set rules and guidelines.\nTend to feel many emotions simultaneously which can lead to anxiety and depression.</string>

    <string name="c_desc">The sub-traits of conscientiousness personality trait are: Well-organized, have strong sense of moral obligation, confident, achievement-striving, self-discipline and cautious.</string>
    <string name="c_strength">Organized and always come into situations prepared.\nAttentive to detail.\nHardworking.\nRarely make impulsive or careless decisions.\nTend to pay attention to detail to make sure they deliver on their promises.</string>
    <string name="c_weakness">Perfectionist.\nMay be excessively serious in some situations.\nInflexible.\nStruggle to be spontaneous.\nTend to have obsessive-compulsive disorder.</string>

    <string name="e_desc">The sub-traits of extraversion personality trait are: Friendly, gregarious, assertive, have high activity level, excitement-seeking and cheerful.</string>
    <string name="e_strength">Tend to relate well to others.\nOften well-liked in their teams and offices.\nForm quick and easy friendships.\nTheir outgoing nature leads to effective group-work.\nUsually very determined, likely to take charge, and confident.</string>
    <string name="e_weakness">May lack independence.\nCan sometimes make others uncomfortable.\nStruggle with keeping their emotions in check.\nMay be inconsiderate or sometimes socially unaware.\nOften unable to make analytical, emotionless judgements.</string>

    <string name="a_desc">The sub-traits of agreeableness personality trait are: Have high trust with people, altruistic, good at cooperation, have high morality, modest and sympathetic.</string>
    <string name="a_strength">Tend to get pleasure from taking care of people.\nGet along well with others.\nAre socially and emotionally intelligent.\nForm friendships easily.\nRefrain to judging people.</string>
    <string name="a_weakness">Struggle to assert their wants, needs and preferences.\nStruggle in situations that require tough decision.\nTend to forget to plan their own advancement.\nOften likely to be taken advantage of.\nTend to overwork themselves due to an inability to delegate properly.</string>

    <string name="n_desc">The sub-traits of neuroticism personality trait are: Anxiety, high anger level, depressed, have high self-consciousness, immoderate and vulnerable.</string>
    <string name="n_strength">Sensitive and aware in a way that some others might not be.\nLikely to be the one who is always looking out for others.\nRealistic.\nHave high self-awareness.\nValue the safety of knowing what to expect over the risk of disappointment from trying to engage in unfamiliar and unproven ways.</string>
    <string name="n_weakness">Dramatic changes in feelings.\nTend to be more anxious when they perceive the situation to be negative.\nTend to experience a lot of stress.\nOverly aware and sensitive about what others think of them.\nTend to self-doubt themselves.</string>

    <string name="emptyPassword">Password is empty!</string>
    <string name="passError">Password should be more than 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="emptyEmail">Email is empty!</string>
    <string name="emailInvalid">Email is not valid!</string>
    <string name="message_title">Congrats!</string>
    <string name="message_body">Your account is created.</string>
    <string name="posbutton">Login</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="question_p1">[ Question 1 – 5 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p2">[ Question 6 – 10 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p3">[ Question 11 – 15 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p4">[ Question 16 – 20 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p5">[ Question 21 – 25 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p6">[ Question 26 – 30 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p7">[ Question 31 – 35 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p8">[ Question 36 – 40 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p9">[ Question 41 – 45 ]</string>
    <string name="question_p10">[ Question 46 – 50 ]</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>